Driver Version: 15.40.0.64.4240
 
Release Version: Production Version


Platform / Operating System(s):   

4th Gen Intel(R) Core(TM) processor family (codename Haswell
 	Microsoft Windows* 10 64
 	
 	
5th Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) processor family (codename Broadwell) 
 	Microsoft Windows* 10 64
 	

Release Date: June 26, 2015


CONTENTS

I.	Product Support
II.	Installation Information
III.	Disclaimer
IV.	Important Note


I.  Product Support


Supports Intel(R) Iris(TM) graphics, Intel(R) Iris(TM) Pro graphics and Intel(R) HD graphics on:  

		
	5th Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor Platform (codename Broadwell) 
	4th Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor Platform (codename Haswell) 

II.  Installation Information      

This document makes references to products developed by Intel. There are some restrictions on how these products may be used, and what information may be disclosed to others. Please read the Disclaimer section and contact your Intel field representative if you would like more information.

III.  Disclaimer

Intel is making no claims of usability, efficacy or warranty. The INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT contained herein completely defines the license and use of this software.

This document contains information on products in the design phase of development. The information here is subject to change without notice. Do not finalize a design with this information.

IV.  Important Note

Your computer is configured to run the WinSAT* test, which determines whether the computer can support the Windows Aero* desktop theme. The test will run after this driver is installed and the computer is restarted. If your computer can support it, the Windows Aero desktop theme will automatically be enabled.

This test will take approximately 10 seconds.

*Other names and brands may be claimed as the property of others.
