INSTALLATION README


Release Version: Production Version

Driver Version: 15.33.8.64.3345

Package: 211621

Intel(R) Graphics Driver: 10.18.10.3345
Intel(R) Display Audio Driver: 6.16.0.3129


Operating System(s):   

Microsoft Windows* 7 64
Microsoft Windows* 8 64
Microsoft Windows* 8.1 64

Release Date: November 01, 2013


CONTENTS OF THIS DOCUMENT

I.	Installation Information
II.	System Requirements
III.	Localized Language Abbreviations
IV.	Installing the Software
V.	Verifying Installation of the Software
VI.	Identifying the Software Version Number
VII.	Installation Switches 
VIII.	Uninstalling the Software
IX.	Intel Software License Agreement
X.	Disclaimer


I.  INSTALLATION INFORMATION

Supports Intel(R) Iris(TM) graphics, Intel(R) Iris(TM) Pro graphics, and Intel(R) HD graphics on: 

	4th Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor Platform
	4th Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor U Series-based Platform
	4th Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor Y Series-based Platform
	3rd Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor Platform
	3rd Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor U Series-based Platform
	3rd Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor Y Series-based Platform
	Intel(R) Pentium(R) Processor 2000/3000/G2000/G2100/G3000 Series
	Intel(R) Celeron(R) Processor 900/1000/2000/G1000 Series


DISCLAIMER: Intel is making no claims of usability, efficacy or warranty.  The INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE
AGREEMENT contained herein completely defines the license
and use of this software.
   
This document contains information on products in the design phase of development. 
The information here is subject to change without notice. Do not finalize a  design with this information.


II.  SYSTEM REQUIREMENTS

1.  The system must contain one of the following Intel chipsets/processors:


	4th Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor Platform
	4th Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor U Series-based Platform
	4th Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor Y Series-based Platform
	3rd Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor Platform
	3rd Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor U Series-based Platform
	3rd Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processor Y Series-based Platform
	Intel(R) Pentium(R) Processor 2000/3000/G2000/G2100/G3000 Series
	Intel(R) Celeron(R) Processor 900/1000/2000/G1000 Series
        	

2.  The software should be installed on systems with at
    least 1 GB of system memory.

3.  There should be sufficient hard disk space in the <TEMP>
    directory on the system in order to install this
    software.

    The drivers included with this distribution package are
    designed to function with all released versions of
    Microsoft Windows* 7 / Windows* 8 OS(s) available at the time of 
    release of this package.

Please check with your system provider to determine the
operating system and Intel chipset used in your system.


III.  LOCALIZED LANGUAGE ABBREVIATIONS

The following list contains the hexadecimal key of all
languages into which the driver has been localized. You may
have to refer to this section while using this document.


0401 -> Arabic
0404 -> Chinese Traditional
041A -> Croatian 
0405 -> Czech
0406 -> Danish
0413 -> Dutch
0409 -> English (United States)
040B -> Finnish
040C -> French (Standard)
0407 -> German
0408 -> Greek
040D -> Hebrew
040E -> Hungarian
0410 -> Italian
0411 -> Japanese
0412 -> Korean
0414 -> Norwegian
0415 -> Polish
0416 -> Portuguese (Brazil)
0816 -> Portuguese (Standard)
0418 -> Romanian
0419 -> Russian
0804 -> Simplified Chinese
041B -> Slovak
0424 -> Slovenian
0C0A -> Spanish
041D -> Swedish
041E -> Thai
041F -> Turkish


IV.  INSTALLING THE SOFTWARE

General Installation Notes:

1.  The operating system must be installed prior to the installation of the 
    driver.

2.  This installation procedure is specific only to the version of driver 
    and installation file included in this release.

3.  This procedure assumes that all of the software associated with this 
    release is located in the same directory.


INSTALLATION INSTRUCTIONS 
------------------------------------------------------------------

To install from a Web download, you will download either a .zip file or an 
.exe file.

a. If it is a .zip file, double-click on the file you downloaded and choose 
   "Extract all files". Browse to a destination folder and choose "Extract".

b. If it is an .exe file, double-click on the file you downloaded and specify a 
   location to extract the  driver files. Click "Unzip" and the files will 
   extract. Click "OK" on the next window, then click "Close". 


------------------------------------------------------------------
  Microsoft Windows* "Setup.exe" Installation
------------------------------------------------------------------

1. Locate the hard drive directory where the driver files are stored 
   using the browser or the Explore feature of Windows*.

2. From this directory, double-click the "Setup.exe" file.

3. The first dialog of the installation user interface will appear. 
   By default, a checkbox is selected to automatically run WinSAT 
   and enable the Windows Aero desktop theme (if supported). 
   Deselect the checkbox if this support should be turned off. 
 
4. Click "Next" to continue.

5. Read the License Agreement and, if you agree with the terms, 
   click "Yes" to proceed.

6. Review the Readme File information and click "Next" to proceed.

7. When the "Setup Progress" is complete, click "Next" to proceed.

8. When the "Setup is Complete" screen appears, click "Finish" to
   complete the installation.
 
  
------------------------------------------------------------------
   Microsoft Windows* "Have Disk" Installation 
------------------------------------------------------------------

1.  Click "Start", right-click "Computer", and click "Properties". 

2.  Click "Device Manager" on the left. 

3.  In the "User Account Control" window, click "Yes".

    IF UPDATING DRIVER GO TO STEP 5

4.  Double-click "Video Controller (VGA Compatible)" if present under 
    "Other Devices". (Go to step 6).

5.  Expand "Display adapters" and double-click the graphics controller.

6.  In the "Driver" tab, click "Update Driver".

7.  Click "Browse my computer for driver software".

8.  Click "Let me pick from a list of device drivers on my computer".
  
9.  Click "Have Disk..." and click "Browse".

10. Browse to the directory where you unzipped the file you 
    downloaded, click the "Graphics" folder, and select the
    "igdlh.INF" file. Click "Open".

11. Click "OK" and click "Next". The operating system will install 
    the driver.
    
12. Click "Close" and click "Yes" to reboot. The driver should now 
    be loaded. 


------------------------------------------------------------------
	Microsoft Windows* Manual Installation Instructions
------------------------------------------------------------------

1.  Click "Start", right-click "Computer", and click "Properties".

2.  Click "Device Manager" on the left.

3.  In the "User Account Control" window, click "Yes".

    IF UPDATING DRIVER GO TO STEP 5

4.  Double-click "Video Controller (VGA Compatible)" if present under 
    "Other Devices". (Go to step 6)

5.  Expand "Display adapters" and double-click the graphics controller.  

6.  In the "Driver" tab, click "Update Driver".

7.  Click "Browse my computer for driver software".

8.  Click directly "Browse".

9.  Browse to the directory where you unzipped the file you downloaded
    and click the "Graphics" folder.

10. Click "OK" and click "Next". The operating system will install the 
    driver if it considers this an upgrade.
    
11. Click "Close" and click "Yes" to reboot. The driver should now 
    be loaded.

------------------------------------------------------------------
	For Intel(R) Display Audio Driver:
------------------------------------------------------------------

1.  Click "Start", right-click "Computer", and click "Properties".

2.  Click "Device Manager" on the left. 

3.  In the "User Account Control" window, click "Yes".

4.  Double-click "Sound, video and game controllers".

5.  If installing from scratch, right-click the "High Definition Audio" 
    controller. If updating the driver, right-click the "Intel(R) 
    Display Audio" controller. Click "Update Driver Software...".

6.  Click "Browse my computer for driver software". 

7.  Click "Let me pick from a list of device drivers on my computer".
  
8.  Click "Have Disk..." and click "Browse".

9.  Browse to the directory where you unzipped the file you 
    downloaded, click the "DisplayAudio" folder, and select the
    "IntcDAud.inf" file. Click "Open" and click "OK".

10. Select "Intel(R) Display Audio" and click "Next". 

11. The operating system will install the driver. Click "Finish" to
    complete the installation. 

12. Click "Yes" to reboot. The driver should now be loaded. 

To determine if the driver has been loaded correctly, refer to the 
Verifying Installation of the Software section below.


V.  VERIFYING INSTALLATION OF THE SOFTWARE

1.  Click "Start", right-click "Computer", and click "Properties".

2.  Click "Device Manager" on the left. 

3.  In the "User Account Control" window, click "Yes".

4.  Expand "Display adapters". The Intel(R) Graphics Driver should 
    be listed. If not, the driver is not installed correctly. 

------------------------------------------------------------------
	For Intel(R) Display Audio Driver:
------------------------------------------------------------------

1.  Click "Start", right-click "Computer", and click "Properties".

2.  Click "Device Manager" on the left.

3.  In the "User Account Control" window, click "Yes".

4.  Expand "Sound, video and game controllers". The "Intel(R) Display 
    Audio" driver should be listed and should not show a yellow bang. 
    If not, the driver is not installed correctly. 

To check the version of the driver, refer to the section below.


VI.  IDENTIFYING THE SOFTWARE VERSION NUMBER

1.  Click "Start", right-click "Computer", and click "Properties".

2.  Click "Device Manager" on the left.

3.  In the "User Account Control" window, click "Yes".

4.  Expand "Display adapters" and double-click the graphics controller.  

5.  In the "Driver" tab, note the Driver Version.

------------------------------------------------------------------
	For Intel(R) Display Audio Driver:
------------------------------------------------------------------

1.  Click "Start", right-click "Computer", and click "Properties".

2.  Click "Device Manager" on the left.

3.  In the "User Account Control" window, click "Yes". 

4.  Expand "Sound, video and game controllers" and double-click 
    "Intel(R) Display Audio".

5.  In the "Driver" tab, click "Driver Details". The function driver 
    (IntcDAud.sys) version should be listed on this screen.


VII.   INSTALLATION SWITCHES

The switches in the Setup.exe file will have the following syntax. 
Switches are not case-sensitive and may be specified in any order 
(except for the -s switch). Switches must be separated by spaces.
SETUP [-b] [-overwrite] [-nowinsat] [-l<LCID>] [-s] [-report <path>] 

GFX-INSTALLATION CUSTOM SWITCHES
-b Forces a system reboot after the installation completes.
In non-silent mode, the absence of this switch will prompt
the user to reboot. In silent mode, the absence of this
switch forces the Setup.exe to complete without rebooting
(the user must manually reboot to conclude the installation
process).

-overwrite Installs the Intel(R) Graphics Driver regardless of 
the version of previously installed driver. In non-silent mode,
the absence of this switch will prompt the user to confirm
overwrite of a newer Intel(R) Graphics Driver. In silent mode, 
the absence of this switch means that the installation will 
abort any attempts to regress the revision of the Intel(R) Graphics 
driver.

-l<LCID> Specifies the language used in the installation user 
interface. Without this switch, the installation user interface 
will be shown in the Display language of the OS by default. 
Hexadecimal values for the supported languages can be found in 
the localized language abbreviations section of this readme.

-s Runs in silent mode. The absence of this switch causes
the installation to be performed in verbose mode.

-report <path> Specifies an alternate location for the log file 
created by a silent installation. By default, the log file is 
created and stored during a silent installation under <root 
directory>\Intel\Logs directory as IntelGFX.log
(<WINDIR>\Temp\IntelGFX.log).

-nowinsat Turns off the automatic support for updating / 
obtaining the WinSAT* DWM score on Windows* during installation. 
In non-silent mode, the absence of this switch will enable 
automatic support for updating the WinSAT* score, but allows 
the option to disable this support with a user accessible 
checkbox shown within the installation user interface. 
In silent mode, the absence of this switch forces an automatic 
run of WinSAT and will enable the Windows* Aero* desktop theme 
(if supported).


VIII.  UNINSTALLING THE SOFTWARE

NOTE: This procedure assumes the above installation process
was successful. This uninstallation procedure is specific
only to the version of the driver and installation files
included in this package.


	FOR INTEL(R) GRAPHICS DRIVER:
------------------------------------------------------------------
1. Click "Start", click "Control Panel" icon, and double-click 
   "Programs and Features".

2. Right-click "Intel(R) Graphics Driver" and select "Uninstall".

3. Click "Next" and "Next" to uninstall the driver.

4. Click "Finish" to restart the computer.


	For INTEL(R) DISPLAY AUDIO DRIVER:
------------------------------------------------------------------

1.  Click "Start", right-click "Computer", and click "Properties".

2.  Click "Device Manager" on the left.

3.  In the "User Account Control" window, click "Yes". 

4.  Expand "Sound, video and game controllers", right-click "Intel(R) 
    Display Audio", and select "Uninstall".

5.  In the "Confirm Device Uninstall" window, click "OK" and the Intel(R)
    Display Audio driver will be uninstalled.


------------------------------------------------------------------
IX.  INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT 
    (OEM / IHV / ISV Distribution & Single User)
------------------------------------------------------------------

IMPORTANT - READ BEFORE COPYING, INSTALLING OR USING: 

Do not use or load software from this site or any associated materials (collectively, the "Software") until you have carefully read the following terms and conditions. By loading or using the Software, you agree to the terms of this Agreement. If you do not wish to so agree, do not install or use the Software.
Please Also Note:
        •	If you are an Original Equipment Manufacturer (OEM), Independent Hardware Vendor (IHV) or Independent Software Vendor (ISV), this complete LICENSE AGREEMENT applies; 
        •	If you are an End-User, then only Exhibit A, the INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT, applies.

For OEMs, IHVs, and ISVs:

LICENSE. Subject to the terms of this Agreement, Intel grants to You a nonexclusive, nontransferable, worldwide, fully paid-up license under Intel's copyrights to:
         •	use, modify and copy Software internally for Your own development and maintenance purposes; and 
         •	modify, copy and distribute Software, including derivative works of the Software, to Your end-users, but only under a license agreement with terms at least as restrictive as those contained in Intel's Final, Single User License Agreement, attached as Exhibit A; and 
         •	modify, copy and distribute the end-user documentation which may accompany the Software, but only in association with the Software. 
If You are not the final manufacturer or vendor of a computer system or software program incorporating the Software, then You may transfer a copy of the Software, including derivative works of the Software (and related end-user documentation) to Your recipient for use in accordance with the terms of this Agreement, provided such recipient agrees to be fully bound by the terms hereof. You shall not otherwise assign, sublicense, lease, or in any other way transfer or disclose Software to any third party. You shall not reverse- compile, disassemble or otherwise reverse-engineer the Software.

You may not subject the Software, in whole or in part, to any license obligations of Open Source Software including without limitation combining or distributing the Software with Open Source Software in a manner that subjects the Software or any portion of the Software provided by Intel hereunder to any license obligations of such Open Source Software. "Open Source Software" means any software that requires as a condition of use, modification and/or distribution of such software that such software or other software incorporated into, derived from or distributed with such software (a) be disclosed or distributed in source code form; or (b) be licensed by the user to third parties for the purpose of making and/or distributing derivative works; or (c) be redistributable at no charge. Open Source Software includes, without limitation, software licensed or distributed under any of the following licenses or distribution models, or licenses or distribution models substantially similar to any of the following:
 (a) GNU’s General Public License (GPL) or Lesser/Library GPL (LGPL), (b) the Artistic License (e.g., PERL), (c) the Mozilla Public License, (d) the Netscape Public License, (e) the Sun Community Source License (SCSL), (f) the Sun Industry Source License (SISL), (g) the Apache Software license and (h) the Common Public License (CPL). 

NO OTHER RIGHTS. The Software is protected by the intellectual property laws of the United States and other countries, and international treaty provisions. Except as otherwise expressly above, Intel grants no express or implied rights under Intel patents, copyrights, trademarks, or other intellectual property rights. Except as expressly stated in this Agreement, no license or right is granted to You directly or by implication, inducement, estoppel or otherwise. Intel shall have the right to inspect or have an independent auditor inspect Your relevant records to verify Your compliance with the terms and conditions of this Agreement

CONFIDENTIALITY. 
If You wish to have a third party consultant or subcontractor ("Contractor") perform work on Your behalf which involves access to or use of Software, You shall obtain a written confidentiality agreement from the Contractor which contains terms and obligations with respect to access to or use of Software no less restrictive than those set forth in this Agreement and excluding any distribution rights, and use for any other purpose. Otherwise, You shall not disclose the terms or existence of this Agreement or use Intel's Name in any publications, advertisements, or other announcements without Intel's prior written consent. You do not have any rights to use any Intel trademarks or logos.

OWNERSHIP OF SOFTWARE AND COPYRIGHTS. 
Title to all copies of the Software remains with Intel or its suppliers. The Software is copyrighted and protected by the laws of the United States and other countries, and international treaty provisions. You may not remove any copyright notices from the Software. Intel may make changes to the Software, or to items referenced therein, at any time without notice, but is not obligated to support or update the Software. Except as otherwise expressly provided, Intel grants no express or implied right under Intel patents, copyrights, trademarks, or other intellectual property rights. You may transfer the Software only if the recipient agrees to be fully bound by these terms and if you retain no copies of the Software.

SUPPORT. 
Intel may make changes to the Software, or to items referenced therein, at any time without notice, but is not obligated to support, update or provide training for the Software. Intel may in its sole discretion offer such services under separate terms at Intel’s then-current rates. You may request additional information on Intel’s service offerings from an Intel sales representative. You agree to be solely responsible to Your End Users for any update or support obligation or other liability which may arise from the distribution of the Software.
EXCLUSION OF OTHER WARRANTIES. EXCEPT AS PROVIDED ABOVE, THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NONINFRINGEMENT, OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  Intel does not warrant or assume responsibility for the accuracy or completeness of any information, text, graphics, links or other items contained within the Software.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. 
IN NO EVENT SHALL INTEL OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, OR LOST INFORMATION) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SOFTWARE, EVEN IF INTEL HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS PROHIBIT EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER LEGAL RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION. THE SOFTWARE LICENSED HEREUNDER IS NOT DESIGNED OR INTENDED FOR USE IN ANY MEDICAL, LIFE SAVING OR LIFE SUSTAINING SYSTEMS, TRANSPORTATION SYSTEMS, NUCLEAR SYSTEMS, OR FOR ANY OTHER MISSION CRITICAL APPLICATION IN WHICH THE FAILURE OF THE SOFTWARE COULD LEAD TO PERSONAL INJURY OR DEATH. YOU SHALL INDEMNIFY AND HOLD INTEL AND THE INTEL PARTIES HARMLESS AGAINST ALL CLAIMS, COSTS, DAMAGES, AND EXPENSES, AND REASONABLE ATTORNEY FEES ARISING OUT OF, DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY, THE DISTRIBUTION OF THE SOFTWARE AND ANY CLAIM OF PRODUCT LIABILITY, PERSONAL INJURY OR DEATH ASSOCIATED WITH ANY UNINTENDED USE, EVEN IF SUCH CLAIM ALLEGES THAT AN INTEL PARTY WAS NEGLIGENT REGARDING THE DESIGN OR MANUFACTURE OF THE SOFTWARE. THE LIMITED REMEDIES, WARRANTY DISCLAIMER AND LIMITED LIABILITY ARE FUNDAMENTAL ELEMENTS OF THE BASIS OF THE BARGAIN BETWEEN INTEL AND YOU. INTEL WOULD NOT BE ABLE TO PROVIDE THE SOFTWARE WITHOUT SUCH LIMITATIONS. 

TERMINATION OF THIS AGREEMENT.
Intel may terminate this Agreement immediately, upon notice from Intel, if You violate its terms. Upon termination, You will immediately destroy the Software (including providing certification of such destruction back to Intel) or return all copies of the Software to Intel. In the event of termination of this Agreement, all licenses granted to You hereunder shall immediately terminate, except for licenses that you have previously distributed to Your end-users pursuant to the license grant above.
 
APPLICABLE LAWS.
Any claims arising under or relating to this Agreement shall be governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of Delaware or federal courts located in Delaware, without regard to principles of conflict of laws. Each Party hereby agrees to jurisdiction and venue in the courts of the State of Delaware for all disputes and litigation arising under or relating to this Agreement. The Parties agree that the United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods is specifically excluded from application to this Agreement. The Parties consent to the personal jurisdiction of the above courts. 

GOVERNMENT RESTRICTED RIGHTS. 
The Software is a "commercial item" as that term is defined in 48 C.F.R. 2.101, consisting of "commercial computer software" and "commercial computer software documentation" as such terms are used in 48 C.F.R. 12.212. Consistent with 48 C.F.R. 12.212 and 48 C.F.R 227.7202-1 through 227.7202-4, You will provide the Software to the U.S. Government as an End User only pursuant to the terms and conditions therein. Contractor or Manufacturer is Intel Corporation, 2200 Mission College Blvd., Santa Clara, CA 95052. 
 
ASSIGNMENT. 
You may not delegate, assign or transfer this Agreement, the license(s) granted or any of Your rights or duties hereunder, expressly, by implication, by operation of law, by way of merger (regardless of whether You are the surviving entity) or acquisition, or otherwise and any attempt to do so, without Intel’s express prior written consent, shall be null and void. Intel may assign this Agreement, and its rights and obligations hereunder, in its sole discretion. 

ENTIRE AGREEMENT. 
The terms and conditions of this Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the parties with respect to the subject matter hereof, and merges and supersedes all prior, contemporaneous agreements, understandings, negotiations and discussions. Neither of the parties hereto shall be bound by any conditions, definitions, warranties, understandings or representations with respect to the subject matter hereof other than as expressly provided for herein. Intel is not obligated under any other agreements unless they are in writing and signed by an authorized representative of Intel. Without limiting the foregoing, terms and conditions on any purchase orders or similar materials submitted by You to Intel, and any terms contained in Intel’s standard acknowledgment form that are in conflict with these terms, shall be of no force or effect. 

ATTORNEYS’ FEES. 
In the event any proceeding or lawsuit is brought by Intel or You in connection with this Agreement, the prevailing party in such proceeding shall be entitled to receive its costs, expert witness fees and reasonable attorneys’ fees, including costs and fees on appeal. 

NO AGENCY. 
Nothing contained herein shall be construed as creating any agency, employment relationship, partnership, principal-agent or other form of joint enterprise between the parties. 

SEVERABILITY. 
In the event that any provision of this Agreement shall be unenforceable or invalid under any applicable law or be so held by applicable court decision, such unenforceability or invalidity shall not render this Agreement unenforceable or invalid as a whole, and, in such event, such provision shall be changed and interpreted so as to best accomplish the objectives of such unenforceable or invalid provision within the limits of applicable law or applicable court decisions. 

WAIVER. 
The failure of either party to require performance by the other party of any provision hereof shall not affect the full right to require such performance at any time thereafter; nor shall the waiver by either party of a breach of any provision hereof be taken or held to be a waiver of the provision itself. 

LANGUAGE. 
This Agreement is in the English language only, which language shall be controlling in all respects, and all versions of this Agreement in any other language shall be for accommodation only and shall not be binding on you or Intel. All communications and notices made or given pursuant to this Agreement, and all documentation and support to be provided, unless otherwise noted, shall be in the English language. 


EXHIBIT “A” 
INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT (Final, Single User)

IMPORTANT - READ BEFORE COPYING, INSTALLING OR USING. 
Do not use or load software from this site or any associated materials (collectively, the "Software") until you have carefully read the following terms and conditions. By loading or using the Software, you agree to the terms of this Agreement. If you do not wish to so agree, do not install or use the Software.

LICENSE. 
You may copy the Software onto a single computer for your personal, or internal business purpose use, and you may make one back-up copy of the Software, subject to these conditions:
         •	You may not copy, modify, rent, sell, distribute or transfer any part of the Software except as provided in this 		Agreement, and you agree to prevent unauthorized copying of the Software. 
         •	You may not reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble the Software. 
         •	You may not sublicense or permit simultaneous use of the Software by more than one user. 
         •	The Software may contain the software or other property of third party suppliers, some of which may be 		identified in, and licensed in accordance with, any enclosed “license.txt” file or other text or file. 


OWNERSHIP OF SOFTWARE AND COPYRIGHTS. 
Title to all copies of the Software remains with Intel or its suppliers. The Software is copyrighted and protected by the laws of the United States and other countries, and international treaty provisions. You may not remove any copyright notices from the Software. Intel may make changes to the Software, or to items referenced therein, at any time without notice, but is not obligated to support or update the Software. Except as otherwise expressly provided, Intel grants no express or implied right under Intel patents, copyrights, trademarks, or other intellectual property rights. You may transfer the Software only if the recipient agrees to be fully bound by these terms and if you retain no copies of the Software.

EXCLUSION OF OTHER WARRANTIES. 
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF ANY KIND INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NONINFRINGEMENT, OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. Intel does not warrant or assume responsibility for the accuracy or completeness of any information, text, graphics, links or other items contained within the Software.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. 
IN NO EVENT SHALL INTEL OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, OR LOST INFORMATION) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SOFTWARE, EVEN IF INTEL HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS PROHIBIT EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER LEGAL RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION.

TERMINATION OF THIS AGREEMENT. 
Intel may terminate this Agreement at any time if you violate its terms. Upon termination, you will immediately destroy the Software or return all copies of the Software to Intel.
 
APPLICABLE LAWS. 
Claims arising under this Agreement shall be governed by the laws of Delaware, excluding its principles of conflict of laws and the United Nations Convention on Contracts for the Sale of Goods. You may not export the Software in violation of applicable export laws and regulations. Intel is not obligated under any other agreements unless they are in writing and signed by an authorized representative of Intel.

GOVERNMENT RESTRICTED RIGHTS. 
The Software is provided with "RESTRICTED RIGHTS." Use, duplication, or disclosure by the Government is subject to restrictions as set forth in FAR52.227-14 and DFAR252.227-7013 et seq. or its successor. Use of the Software by the Government constitutes acknowledgment of Intel's proprietary rights therein. Contractor or Manufacturer is Intel Corporation, 2200 Mission College Blvd., Santa Clara, CA 95052. 

 
SLA/OEM/IHV/RBK/ April 23, 2004


X.  DISCLAIMER

Intel is making no claims of usability, efficacy or warranty.The INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT contained 
herein completely defines the license and use of this software.

Information in this document is provided in connection with Intel products. Except as expressly stated in the INTEL
SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT contained herein, no license,express or implied, by estoppel or otherwise, to any
intellectual property rights is granted by this document.Except as provided in Intel's Terms and Conditions of Sale
for such products, Intel assumes no liability whatsoever,and Intel disclaims any express or implied warranty,
relating to sale and/or use of Intel products, including liability or warranties relating to fitness for a 
particular purpose, merchantability or infringement of any patent, copyright or other intellectual property right. 
Intel products are not intended for use in medical,lifesaving, or life-sustaining applications.

Intel Corporation disclaims all warranties and liabilities for the use of this document, the software 
and the information contained herein, and assumes no responsibility for any errors which may appear in this
document or the software, nor does Intel make a commitment to update the information or software contained herein. Intel reserves the right to make changes to this document or software at any time, without
notice.


* Other names and brands may be claimed as the property of 
others.

Copyright (C) 2013 Intel Corporation.  All rights reserved.
------------------------------------------------------------------

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.

Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

Neither the name of 3Dlabs Inc. Ltd. nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS"AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING,
BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

Copyright (C) 2002-2013  3Dlabs Inc. Ltd.
All rights reserved

